National Railroad Adjustment Board Case Files 5837
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Award No. 2940. Docket No. 2781. Southern Railway. JF Joly, Jr., 1971-1973 (Box 51, Folder 19)
- Award No. 2942. Docket No. 2835. Grand Trunk Western. WN Roddy., 1972-1973 (Box 51, Folder 20)
- Award No. 2943. Docket No. 2836. Norfolk and Western Railway Co. FC Buczek., 1972-1973 (Box 51, Folder 21)
- Award No. 2944. Docket No. 2849. Grand Trunk Western Railroad Co. FR Hoskin., 1972-1973 (Box 51, Folder 22)
- Award No. 2945. Docket No. 2850. Baltimore and Ohio Railroad. LJ Boyer., 1972-1973 (Box 51, Folder 23)
- Award No. 2946. Docket No. 2851. Union Belt of Detroit. CW Chamberlain., 1972-1973 (Box 51, Folder 24)
- Award No. 2947. Docket No. 2856. Southern Railway System. JL Lomb., 1972-1973 (Box 51, Folder 25)
- Award No. 2948. Docket No. 2862. Texas and Pacific Railway. JG Clements., 1972-1973 (Box 51, Folder 26)
- Award No. 2949. Docket No. 2988. Norfolk and Western Railway Co. EH Gierszewski., 1973 (Box 51, Folder 27)
- Award No. 2950. Docket No. 2989. Norfolk and Western Railway Co. EH Gierszewski., 1973 (Box 51, Folder 28)
- Award No. 2955. Docket No. 2015. Fort Worth ad Denver. JT Ledford., 1972-1973 (Box 52, Folder 1)
- Award No. 2956. Docket No. 2919. Fort Worth and Denver. JW Spivey., 1972-1973 (Box 52, Folder 2)
- Award No. 2957. Docket No. 2916. Forth Worth and Denver. GE Milford., 1972-1973 (Box 52, Folder 3)
- Award No. 2958. Docket No. 2917. Fort Worth and Denver. JT Ledford., 1972-1973 (Box 52, Folder 4)
- Award No. 2959. Docket No. 2918. Fort Worth and Denver. JW Spivey., 1972-1973 (Box 52, Folder 5)
- Award No. 2960. Docket No. 2923. Baltimore and Ohio. JW Willington., 1972-1973 (Box 52, Folder 6)
- Award No. 2961. Docket No. 2924. Claim, Pittsburgh Yard. Baltimore and Ohio. RT Johnson., 1972-1973 (Box 52, Folder 7)
- Award No. 2965. Docket No. 2948. Penn Central. RT Coster., 1973 (Box 52, Folder 8)
- Award No. 2966. Docket No. 3006. Chicago, Milwaukee, St Paul and Pacific Railroad Co. JJ Fons., 1973 (Box 52, Folder 9)
- Award No. 2968. Docket No. 2933. Penn Central. S Ferrise., 1972-1973 (Box 52, Folder 10)
- Award No. 2969. Docket No. 2945. Seaboard Coast Line Railroad Co. JF Smith., 1973 (Box 52, Folder 11)
- Award No. 2970. Docket No. 2949. Penn Central. GE Field., 1972-1973 (Box 52, Folder 12)
- Award No. 2971. Docket No. 2950. Chicago and North Western Railroad Co. Various Yardmasters., 1972-1973 (Box 52, Folder 13)
- Award No. 2972. Docket No. 2952. Chicago and North Western Railroad Co. LK Ballargeon., 1972-1973 (Box 52, Folder 14)
- Award No. 2974. Docket No. 2956. Union Belt of Detroit. Paul Gregory., 1972-1973 (Box 52, Folder 15)
- Award No. 2976. Docket No. 2963. Penn Central. G Potash, Jr., 1972-1973 (Box 52, Folder 16)
- Award No. 2977. Docket No. 964. Penn Central. Various Yardmasters' Time Claims., 1973 (Box 52, Folder 17)
- Award No. 2995. Docket No. 2927. Houston Belt and Terminal Railway Co. JA Paluch., 1972-1973 (Box 52, Folder 18)
- Award No. 2984. Docket No. 2957. Chicago and North Western. R Olson., 1973 (Box 52, Folder 19)
- Award No. 2996. Docket No. 2935. Houston Belt and Terminal. JA Paluch., 1972-1973 (Box 52, Folder 20)
- Award No. 2997. Docket No. 2936. Houston Belt and Terminal Co. JA Paluch., 1972-1973 (Box 52, Folder 21)
- Award No. 2999. Docket No. 2980. Seaboard Coast Line Railroad Co. WH McGowan., 1973 (Box 52, Folder 22)
- Award No. 3000. Docket No. 2986. Penn Central. LL Sheldon. Harrisburg Division Files, RYA-H-11/71., 1973 (Box 52, Folder 23)
  Case 4-7 and 11-71. Docket 403. Philadelphia Territory.
- Award No. 3002. Docket No. 2994. Norfolk and Western. Western Region. RH Stehman., 1973 (Box 52, Folder 24)
- Award No. 2311. Docket No. 2317. The Pennsylvania Railroad Co. DM Ward., 1967 (Box 53, Folder 1)
- Award No. 2312. Docket No. 2318. Norfolk and Western. JJ Rudnick., 1967 (Box 53, Folder 2)
- Award No. 2320. Docket No. 2402. Lehigh Valley. Michael Kodak., 1968 (Box 53, Folder 3)
- Award No. 2332. Docket No. 2265. Louisville and Nashville. RL Cooper., 1967 (Box 53, Folder 4)
- Award No. 2342. Docket No. 2369. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe. JW Hammer., 1968 (Box 53, Folder 5)
- Award No. 2343. Docket No. 2374. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe. TJ Hylek., 1968 (Box 53, Folder 6)
- Award No. 2344. Docket No. 2375. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe. JL Myrick., 1968 (Box 53, Folder 7)
- Award No. 2348. Docket No. 2400. Terminal Railroad Association of St Louis. RW Gunter., 1968 (Box 53, Folder 8)
- Award No. 2355. Docket No. 2430. Lehigh Valley Railroad. RJ Farley., 1968 (Box 53, Folder 9)
- Award No. 2356. Docket No. 2431. Lehigh Valley Railroad. RJ Farley., 1968 (Box 53, Folder 10)
- Award No. 2366. Docket No. 2347. Southern Railway. HL Davis., 1967-1968 (Box 53, Folder 11)
- Award No. 2367. Docket No. 2378. Baltimore and Ohio Railroad. HB Ridenour., 1968 (Box 53, Folder 12)
- Award No. 2370. Docket No. 2382. Lehigh Valley Railroad. RJ Farley., 1968 (Box 53, Folder 13)
- Award No. 2371. Docket No. 2383. Lehigh Valley Railroad Co. RJ Farley., 1968 (Box 53, Folder 14)
- Award No. 2372. Docket No. 2385. Long Island Railroad. Schulz, Bandell and Frantz., 1968 (Box 53, Folder 15)
- Award No. 2374. Docket No. 2401. Baltimore and Ohio. EF Thompson., 1968 (Box 53, Folder 16)
- Award No. 2376. Docket No. 2407. Lehigh Valley. LE Scruitsky., 1968 (Box 53, Folder 17)
- Award No. 2377. Docket No. 2408. Lehigh Valley. Michael G Griffin., 1968 (Box 53, Folder 18)
- Award No. 2378. Docket No. 2413. Norfolk and Western. HO Duncan., 1968 (Box 53, Folder 19)
- Award No. 2381. Docket No. 2419. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe. RE Fleming, CD Hanson, et al., 1968 (Box 53, Folder 20)
- Award No. 2384. Docket No. 2370. Houston Belt and Terminal Co., 1968 (Box 53, Folder 21)
- Award No. 2385. Docket No. 2379. Chicago and North Western Railway Co. Keefe, Barden, Wockenfuss and Green., 1968 (Box 53, Folder 22)
- Award No. 2390. Docket No. 2377. Chicago and North Western Railway. Swensky, Rasmussen and Manrose., 1968 (Box 53, Folder 23)
- Award No. 2392. Docket No. 2415. Missouri Pacific Railroad. WW Taylor., 1968 (Box 53, Folder 24)
- Award No. 2393. Docket No. 2418. Norfolk and Western. James C Kelley. Sick Pay., 1968 (Box 53, Folder 25)
- Orders of Regional Directors. Decisions of US Railroad Labor Board. Orders and Rulings of ICC. Awards of Fourth Division., 1941 (Box 53, Folder 26)
  Columbus, Ohio. August 1 1941.
- Award No. 2258. Docket No. 2224. Grand Trunk Western. A Strevett., 1966-1967 (Box 54, Folder 1)
- Award No. 2265. Docket No. 2241. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe. HE Radford, et al., 1967 (Box 54, Folder 2)
- Award No. 2259. Docket No. 2230. Grand Trunk Western Railroad Co. Palmer., 1967 (Box 54, Folder 3)
- Award No. 2260. Docket No. 2231. Lehigh Valley Railroad Co. KW Snyder., 1967 (Box 54, Folder 4)
- Award No. 2261. Docket No. 2232. Lehigh Valley Railroad. KW Snyder., 1966-1967 (Box 54, Folder 5)
- Award No. 2263. Docket No. 2237. Missouri Pacific. Various Yardmasters., 1966-1967 (Box 54, Folder 6)
- Award No. 2264. Docket No. 2240. Pennsylvania Railroad. Central Region. System Docket No. 167., 1967 (Box 54, Folder 7)
- Award No. 2266. Docket No. 2242. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe, WG Rusk., 1967 (Box 54, Folder 8)
- Award No. 2268. Docket No. 2245. Pennsylvania Railroad. DW Orr., 1967 (Box 54, Folder 9)
- Carrier Exhibits and McCrory Hearing Transcript., 1964 (Box 54, Folder 10)
- Award No. 2269. Docket No. 2246. Hearing Transcript. LL McCrory Case., 1964 (Box 54, Folder 11)
- Award No. 2269. Docket No. 2246. Pennsylvania Railroad. LL McCrory., 1967 (Box 54, Folder 12)
- Award No. 2272. Docket No. 2366. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe. 16 Yardmasters., 1968 (Box 54, Folder 13)
- Award No. 2273. Docket No. 2367. Chicago, Milwaukee, St Paul and Pacific. WL Gilman., 1967 (Box 54, Folder 14)
- Award No. 2275. Docket No. 2373. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe., 1968 (Box 54, Folder 15)
- Award No. 2276. Docket No. 2384. Union Pacific Railroad. Pettet and Simpson., 1968 (Box 54, Folder 16)
- Award No. 2277. Docket No. 2388. Southern Railway System. BA Young, Spencer, N Car., 1967-1968 (Box 54, Folder 17)
- Award No. 2283. Docket No. 2277. Boston and Maine Corporation. LH Poisson., 1967 (Box 54, Folder 18)
- Award No. 2290. Docket No. 2287. Northern Pacific. BB Ball., 1967 (Box 54, Folder 19)
- Award No. 2299. Docket No. 2297. Erie-Lackawanna. E Gavin, J Dunn, J Kingsley., 1967 (Box 54, Folder 20)
- Award No. 2300. Docket No. 2252. Lehigh Valley. 3rd trick Bethlehem Yard. AN Lukachek., 1967 (Box 54, Folder 21)
- Award No. 2301. Docket No. 2253. Lehigh Valley. Wilkes Barre Yard. John P Schroder., 1967 (Box 54, Folder 22)
- Award No. 2303. Docket No. 2264. Washington Terminal. AW Hurley., 1967 (Box 54, Folder 23)
- Award No. 2304. Docket No. 2270. Grand Trunk Western. RK Russell., 1967 (Box 54, Folder 24)
- Award No. 2308. Docket No. 2314. Pennsylvania Railroad. H Abbott., 1967-1968 (Box 54, Folder 25)
- Award No. 2309. Docket No. 2315. Pennsylvania Railroad. CA Lucas., 1967-1968 (Box 54, Folder 26)
- Award No. 2310. Docket No. 2316. The Pennsylvania Railroad Co. Fred Gilmore., 1967 (Box 54, Folder 27)
- Award No. 1789. Docket No. 1773. Baltimore and Ohio Railroad Co. H Alexander., 1961-1963 (Box 55, Folder 1)
- Award No. 1793. Docket No. 1780. Baltimore and Ohio Chicago Terminal Railroad Co., 1961-1962 (Box 55, Folder 2)
- Award No. 1819. Docket No. 1825. Chicago Rock Island and Pacific Railroad Co. JE Gallipean., 1962-1963 (Box 55, Folder 3)
- Award No. 1820. Docket No. 1846. Pittsburgh and Lake Erie Railroad Co. HL Cassel., 1962-1963 (Box 55, Folder 4)
- Award No. 1821. Docket No. 1855. Rock Island Railroad. CW Taylor., 1962-1963 (Box 55, Folder 5)
- Award No. 1822. Docket No. 1856. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe. Bunch and Graham., 1963 (Box 55, Folder 6)
- Award No. 1826. Docket No. 1871. IRRA. JE Brooks., 1963 (Box 55, Folder 7)
- Award No. 1827. Docket No. 1750. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway Co. DE Parsons., 1962 (Box 55, Folder 8)
- Award No. 1828. Docket No. 1751. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe. DE Parsons., 1962 (Box 55, Folder 9)
- Award No. 1829. Docket No. 1752. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe. WG Rusk., 1961-1962 (Box 55, Folder 10)
- Award No. 1830. Docket No. 1753. Chicago and North Western. Vernon R Heagle., 1961-1962 (Box 55, Folder 11)
- Award No. 1831. Docket No. 1754. Florida East Coast Railroad Co. DJ Kelley., 1962 (Box 55, Folder 12)
- Award No. 1834. Docket No. 1769. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railroad. HG Woolson et al., 1961-1962 (Box 55, Folder 13)
- Award No. 1835. Docket No. 1775. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe. Bullard and Dawes., 1961-1964 (Box 55, Folder 14)
- Award No. 1836. Docket No. 1782. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe. McGurk and Sullivan., 1958-1963 (Box 55, Folder 15)
- Award No. 1839. Docket No. 1791. Chicago Great Western Railway. WR Seymour., 1961-1965 (Box 55, Folder 16)
- Award No. 1842. Docket No. 1797. Washington Terminal Co. H Cornett., 1962-1963 (Box 55, Folder 17)
- Award No. 1843. Docket No. 1798. Washington Terminal Co. CW Rogers., 1962-1963 (Box 55, Folder 18)
- Award No. 1844. Docket No. 1799. Washington Terminal Co. CW Rogers., 1962-1963 (Box 55, Folder 19)
- Award No. 1845. Docket No. 1807. Terminal Railroad Association. J Finkelstein., 1961-1963 (Box 55, Folder 20)
- Award No. 1846. Docket No. 1808. Terminal Railroad Association. HR Chester., 1961-1963 (Box 55, Folder 21)
- Award No. 1948. Docket No. 1822. Washington Terminal Railroad. RE Gremes., 1962-1963 (Box 55, Folder 22)
- Award No. 1849. Docket No. 1823. Washington Terminal Co. TT Caskey., 1962-1963 (Box 55, Folder 23)
- Award No. 1741. Docket No. 1719. Pennsylvania Railroad. JT Jump., 1961-1962 (Box 56, Folder 1)
- Award No. 1745. Docket No. 1647. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe. RD Butler., 1960-1961 (Box 56, Folder 2)
- Award No. 1747. Docket No. 1661. Grand Trunk Western Railroad. JM Johnson., 1961 (Box 56, Folder 3)
- Award No. 1746. Docket No. 1650. Grand Trunk Western. MT Perron., 1961 (Box 56, Folder 4)
- Award No. 1748. Docket No. 1670. Houston Belt and Terminal Railway Co. BC Adams., 1962-1963 (Box 56, Folder 5)
- Award No. 1749. Docket No. 1690. Houston Belt and Terminal Railway Co. DR Page., 1961-1964 (Box 56, Folder 6)
- Award No. 1750. Docket No. 1691. Houston Belt and Terminal Railway Co. DR Page., 1961-1963 (Box 56, Folder 7)
- Award No. 1751. Docket No. 1693. Houston Belt and Terminal Co. WT Dunlop., 1960-1963 (Box 56, Folder 8)
- Award No. 1752. Docket No. 1694. Houston Belt and Terminal Co. WT Dunlop., 1960-1963 (Box 56, Folder 9)
- Award No. 1753. Docket No. 1696. Houston Belt and Terminal Co. BC Adams., 1961-1962 (Box 56, Folder 10)
- Award No. 1754. Docket No. 1697. Houston Belt and Terminal Co. BC Adams., 1961 (Box 56, Folder 11)
- Award No. 1757. Docket No. 1706. Norfolk and Western Railroad. Meadow and Johnson., 1960-1962 (Box 56, Folder 12)
- Award No. 1759. Docket No. 1714. Houston Belt and Terminal Railway Co. WC Gibbs., 1961-1962 (Box 56, Folder 13)
- Award No. 1761. Docket No. 1721. Grand Trunk Western. HJ Graves., 1961-1962 (Box 56, Folder 14)
- Award No. 1769. Docket No. 1834. Atchison Topeka and Santa Fe., 1962-1963 (Box 56, Folder 15)
- Award No. 1771. Docket No. 1838. New York, Chicago and St Louis. Yardmaster Chambers., 1962-1963 (Box 56, Folder 16)
- Award No. 1772. Docket No.1686. Norfolk Southern Railway Co. CT Smith, Jr., 1961-1962 (Box 56, Folder 17)
- Award No. 1773. Docket No. 1710. Norfolk Southern Railway Co. RH Porter., 1962 (Box 56, Folder 18)
- Award No. 1775. Docket No. 1644. Terminal Railroad Association. JH Boyer., 1961-1964 (Box 56, Folder 19)
- Award No. 1776. Docket No. 1675. Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific Railroad Co. Williams., 1960-1962 (Box 56, Folder 20)
- Award No. 1777. Docket No. 1687. Central of Georgia. AE Meyer., 1961-1963 (Box 56, Folder 21)
- Award No. 1781. Docket No. 1724. Baltimore and Ohio Railroad. FA Zimmerman., 1962-1963 (Box 56, Folder 22)
- Award No. 1784. Docket No. 1736. Louisville and Nashville Railroad. RW Cook., 1961-1963 (Box 56, Folder 23)
- Award No. 1788. Docket No. 1757. Chicago Great Western. FD Shea., 1963 (Box 56, Folder 24)
- Award No. 2147. Docket No. 2121. Pennsylvania Railroad. AJ Lynch at Buffalo., 1964-1966 (Box 57, Folder 1)
- Award No. 2150. Docket No. 2124. Baltimore and Ohio Railroad Co. JF Fleig., 1966 (Box 57, Folder 2)
- Award No. 2151. Docket No. 2125. Pennsylvania Railroad. GD Yontz, Jr., 1966 (Box 57, Folder 3)
- Award No. 2152. Docket No. 2127. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe. BJ Armstrong, WR Freeman, KM Clark., 1965-1966 (Box 57, Folder 4)
- Award No. 2155. Docket No. 2129. Pennsylvania Railroad. CA Chada., 1965-1966 (Box 57, Folder 5)
- Award No. 2160. Docket No. 2146. Pennsylvania Railroad. LR Bryant., 1965-1966 (Box 57, Folder 6)
- Award No. 2163. Docket No. 2131. The Washington Terminal. RS Barton., 1966 (Box 57, Folder 7)
- Award No. 2164. Docket No. 2132. Union Belt of Detroit. MH Cozzens., 1965-1968 (Box 57, Folder 8)
- Award No. 2165. Docket No. 2134. Baltimore and Ohio Railroad. RJ Smith, M Novasel, EP Evans., 1965-1966 (Box 57, Folder 9)
- Award No. 2170. Docket No. 2154. Chicago and North Western Railway Co. WV Arter., 1964-1966 (Box 57, Folder 10)
- Award No. 2171. Docket No. 2187. Chicago and North Western Railway Co. V Lund., 1964-1966 (Box 57, Folder 11)
- Award No. 2175. Docket No. 2141. Pennsylvania Railroad. CE Thomas., 1965-1966 (Box 57, Folder 12)
- Award No. 2177. Docket No. 2147. Pennsylvania Railroad. HN Stewart. Subject 18650YM., 1965-1966 (Box 57, Folder 13)
- Award No. 2180. Docket No. 2153. Grand Trunk Western Railroad. DP Jones., 1966 (Box 57, Folder 14)
- Award No. 2182. Docket No. 2158. Norfolk and Western. DC Seipel., 1966 (Box 57, Folder 15)
- Award No. 2183. Docket No. 2159. Norfolk and Western. DC Seipel., 1966 (Box 57, Folder 16)
- Award No. 2189. Docket No. 2160. Soo Line Railroad. JP See., 1966 (Box 57, Folder 17)
- Award No. 2190. Docket No. 2162. Pennsylvania Railroad Co. AJ Strubel., 1966-1967 (Box 57, Folder 18)
- Award No. 2191. Docket No. 2165. Erie-Lackawanna. JV Lindner., 1966 (Box 57, Folder 19)
- Award No. 2192. Docket No. 2166. Pennsylvania Railroad Co. 59th Street Zone Yardmasters., 1966-1967 (Box 57, Folder 20)
- Award No. 2193. Docket No. 2168. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe. WH Teel., 1966 (Box 57, Folder 21)
- Railroad Correspondence., 1958 (Box 58, Folder 1)
- Award No. 1363. Docket No. 1357. Chicago and North Western. Miller Claim., 1958 (Box 58, Folder 2)
- Award No. 1364. Docket No. 1358. Chicago and North Western. WJ Snyder., 1958-1959 (Box 58, Folder 3)
- Award No. 1365. Docket No. 1359. Chicago and North Western. LJ Stift., 1958-1959 (Box 58, Folder 4)
- Award No. 1366. Docket No. 1365. Chicago and North Western. John Pasicznyk, HW Johnson, James R McTie, et al., 1958-1959 (Box 58, Folder 5)
- Award No. 1377. Docket No. 1311. Chicago and North Western. Altoona, Wisconsin. RH Buckholtz., 1958-1959 (Box 58, Folder 6)
- Award No. 1378. Docket No. 1312. Chicago and North Western. Altoona, Wisconsin. JP Hagen., 1957-1958 (Box 58, Folder 7)
- Award No. 1379. Docket No. 1313. Chicago and North Western. Altoona, Wisconsin. DO McDonald., 1957-1959 (Box 58, Folder 8)
- Award No. 1380. Docket No. 1314. Chicago and North Western. WJ Bohn., 1958-1960 (Box 58, Folder 9)
- Award No. 1381. Docket No. 1315. Chicago and North Western. CT Phipps., 1957-1960 (Box 58, Folder 10)
- Award No. 1382. Docket No. 1316. Chicago and North Western. Van Lanschoot., 1958-1960 (Box 58, Folder 11)
- Award No. 1383. Docket No. 1317. Chicago and North Western. GF Koenen., 1958 (Box 58, Folder 12)
- Award No. 1384. Docket No. 1334. Chicago, Milwaukee, St Paul and Pacific Railroad Co. Quenton Hunter., 1958 (Box 58, Folder 13)
- Award No. 1390. Docket No. 1343. Washington Terminal Railroad. H Cornett., 1956-1959 (Box 58, Folder 14)
- Award No. 1389. Docket No. 1406. Baltimore and Ohio Claim. Gray Yard. Abolishment of Yardmaster Position., 1958-1959 (Box 58, Folder 15)
- Award No. 1391. Docket No. 1351. Chicago and North Western Railway. EJ Rule., 1958 (Box 58, Folder 16)
- Award No. 1392. Docket No. 1367. Missouri-Kansas-Texas Railroad Co. RG Leach Claim., 1958-1959 (Box 58, Folder 17)
- Award No. 1404. Docket No. 1410. Baltimore and Ohio Claims. Granger et al., 1958-1959 (Box 58, Folder 18)
- Award No. 1414. Docket No. 1404. Pittsburgh and Lake Erie. EW Bristol., 1958-1959 (Box 58, Folder 19)
- Award No. 1415. Docket No. 1405. Pittsburgh and Lake Erie. CM Miller., 1958-1959 (Box 58, Folder 20)
- Award No. 1438. Docket No. 1430. Missouri-Kansas-Texas Railroad. JF Barron., 1958-1960 (Box 58, Folder 21)
- Award No. 1439. Docket No. 1431. Missouri-Kansas-Texas. Reestablishment of Position No. 9182. Ney Yards, Fort Worth, Texas., 1959 (Box 58, Folder 22)
- Award No. 1667. Docket No. 1720. Terminal Railroad Association. GW Solomon., 1961-1962 (Box 59, Folder 1)
- Award No. 1670. Docket No. 1770. Chicago and North Western Railway. Hansen et al., 1961-1962 (Box 59, Folder 2)
- Award No. 1671. Docket No. 1783. Chicago River and Indiana Railroad. WJ Brischke., 1960-1962 (Box 59, Folder 3)
- Award No. 1672. Docket No. 1784. Chicago River and Indiana Railroad Co. WJ Brischke., 1961-1962 (Box 59, Folder 4)
- Award No. 1673. Docket No. 1785. Chicago River and Indiana Railroad Co. WJ Brischke., 1962 (Box 59, Folder 5)
- Award No. 1674. Docket No. 1786. Chicago River and Indiana Railroad Co. WJ Brischke., 1961-1962 (Box 59, Folder 6)
- Award No. 1675. Docket No. 1787. Chicago River and Indiana Railroad Co. WJ Brischke., 1961-1962 (Box 59, Folder 7)
- Award No. 1676. Docket No. 1788. Chicago River and Indiana Railroad Co. WJ Brischke., 1962 (Box 59, Folder 8)
- Award No. 1677. Docket No. 1789. Chicago River and Indiana Railroad Co. WJ Brischke., 1962 (Box 59, Folder 9)
- Award No. 1678. Docket No. 1790. Chicago River and Indiana Railroad Co. WJ Brischke., 1961-1962 (Box 59, Folder 10)
- Award No. 1679. Docket No. 1792. St Louis - San Francisco Railway Co. BR Davis., 1962 (Box 59, Folder 11)
- Award No. 1680. Docket No. 1577. Chicago, Milwaukee, St Paul and Pacific Railroad Co. JO Oyer., 1960-1962 (Box 59, Folder 12)
- Award No. 1681. Docket No. 1664. Chicago, Milwaukee, St Paul and Pacific Railroad Co. Emory Hansen., 1961-1962 (Box 59, Folder 13)
- Award No. 1682. Docket No. 1622. Grand Trunk Western Railroad Co. MB Newman., 1960-1961 (Box 59, Folder 14)
- Award No. 1683. Docket No. 1642. Grand Trunk Western Railroad Co. AJ Woldanski., 1960-1961 (Box 59, Folder 15)
- Award No. 1684. Docket No. 1643. Grand Trunk Western Railroad Co. WC Abbey., 1960-1961 (Box 59, Folder 16)
- Award No. 1691. Docket No. 1585. Grand Trunk Western Railroad Co. WH Skinner., 1960-1961 (Box 59, Folder 17)
- Award No. 1692. Docket No. 1625. Chicago, Burlington and Quincy Railroad. AE Broch., 1959-1961 (Box 59, Folder 18)
- Award No. 1693. Docket No. 1626. Chicago, Burlington and Quincy Railroad. HA Spear., 1960-1961 (Box 59, Folder 19)
- Award No. 1694. Docket No. 1627. Chicago, Burlington and Quincy Railroad. WB Metten., 1960-1961 (Box 59, Folder 20)
- Award No. 1700. Docket No. 1795. Pittsburgh and Lake Erie Railroad. WM Wiseman., 1962 (Box 59, Folder 21)
- Award No. 1701. Docket No. 1796. Pittsburgh and Lake Erie. RF O'Rourke., 1961-1962 (Box 59, Folder 22)
- Award No. 1702. Docket No. 1800. Pittsburgh and Lake Erie. GT Funkhouser., 1962 (Box 59, Folder 23)
- Award No. 1703. Docket No. 1804. Pittsburgh and Lake Erie Railroad Co. RV Marchand., 1961-1962 (Box 59, Folder 24)
- Award No. 1704. Docket No. 1805. Chicago and North Western Railway Co. HF Anderson., 1961-1962 (Box 59, Folder 25)
- Award No. 1705. Docket No. 1806. Chicago and North Western Railway Co. CF Tehan., 1961-1962 (Box 59, Folder 26)
- Award No. 1706. Docket No. 1809. Chicago, Milwaukee, St Paul and Pacific. Robert Reis., 1961-1962 (Box 59, Folder 27)
- Award No. 1709. Docket No. 1554. Davenport, Rock Island and North Western Railway Co., 1959-1961 (Box 59, Folder 28)
- Award No. 1710. Docket No. 1633. Pennsylvania Railroad. AL George., 1960-1961 (Box 59, Folder 29)
- Award No. 1711. Docket No. 1653. Pennsylvania Railroad Co. RP Sturges., 1960-1961 (Box 59, Folder 30)
- Award No. 1715. Docket No. 1673. Spokane, Portland and Seattle Railway Co. Rafferty and Elson., 1961 (Box 59, Folder 31)
- Award No. 1723. Docket No. 1618. Pennsylvania Railroad. JR McCabe., 1961 (Box 59, Folder 32)
- Award No. 1724. Docket No. 1748. Pennsylvania Railroad. RS Lowe., 1961-1962 (Box 59, Folder 33)
- Award No. 1725. Docket No. 1801. Pittsburgh and Lake Erie. RE Livengood., 1961-1963 (Box 59, Folder 34)
- Award No. 1726. Docket No. 1802. Pittsburgh and Lake Erie. GT Funkhouser., 1963 (Box 59, Folder 35)
- Award No. 1727. Docket No. 1803. Pittsburgh and Lake Erie. BF Husband., 1961-1963 (Box 59, Folder 36)
- Award No. 1728. Docket No. 1817. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe. DF Cordes., 1960-1962 (Box 59, Folder 37)
- Award No. 1729. Docket No. 1818. Norfolk Southern Railway Co. JM McNally., 1959-1963 (Box 59, Folder 38)
- Award No. 1606. Docket No. 1556. Missouri-Kansas-Texas Railroad. JH Lockhart and AJ West., 1960-1962 (Box 60, Folder 1)
- Award No. 1612. Docket No. 1594. Missouri-Kansas-Texas Railroad. RL Brown., 1960-1962 (Box 60, Folder 2)
- Award No. 1614. Docket No. 1559. Missouri Pacific Railroad Co. CE Sells and JA Stanley., 1959 (Box 60, Folder 3)
- Award No. 1618. Docket No. 1668. Houston Belt and Terminal Railway Co. WJ Dunlop., 1961-1962 (Box 60, Folder 4)
- Award No. 1619. Docket No. 1669. Houston Belt and Terminal Co. Elmer Moore., 1960-1961 (Box 60, Folder 5)
- Award No. 1620. Docket No. 1692. Houston Belt and Terminal Railway Co. AL Sarvis., 1960-1962 (Box 60, Folder 6)
- Award No. 1621. Docket No. 1695. Houston Belt and Terminal Railway Co. JA Mullins., 1960-1961 (Box 60, Folder 7)